Guide to the Edwin Warriner Papers and Photographs, 1790-1958 1977.255
Brooklyn Historical Society
- 1. Notes and Ephemera, 1791-1940; 5.42 Linear Feet
  - Brooklyn: Sands Street M. E. Church (72C) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn: Scandinavian M. E. Church (73) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn: Second Church (73-1/2) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn: Second Primitive Meth Church (73-2/3) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn: Simpson M. E. Church (75) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn: Sixth Ave M. E. Church (76) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn: South Brooklyn M. E. Church (77) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn: South Brooklyn Meth. Prot. Church (77-1/2) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn: South Fifth St M. E. Church (E.D.) (78) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn: South Second Street M. E. Church (E.D.) (79) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Brooklyn: South Third Street M.E. Church (E.D.) (80) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Brooklyn: Summerfield (Wash. Ave) M. E. Church (81) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn: Sumner Ave M. E. Church (81B) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Brooklyn: Swedish Immanuel M. E. Church (81C) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn: Tabernacle M. E. Church (E.D.) (81D) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brooklyn: Third Primitive Meth Church (82) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brooklyn: Throop Ave M. E. Church (82A) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brooklyn: Tompkins Ave, see Wesley M. E. Church (82B) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brooklyn: Tompkins Square M. E. Church (82C) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brooklyn: Trinity Meth. Prot. Church (82D) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brooklyn: (The True) Wesleyan Meth. Church (83) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Brooklyn: Union Ave M. E. Mission (E.D.) (84) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn: Wallabout M. E. Church (85) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn: Warren Street M. E. Church (86) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Brooklyn: Washington Street M.E Church (87) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Brooklyn: Welcome Primitive Meth Church (87-1/2) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Brooklyn: Wesley M. E. Church, see Willoughby Ave (88) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Brooklyn: Wesley M. E. Church (E.D.) (89) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Brooklyn: Wesley M. E. Church, first called Goodsell Mission (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Brooklyn: Willoughby Ave M. E. Church (90B) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Brooklyn: Wychoff St German M.E. Church (91) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Brooklyn: Yates Place German M. E. Church (91-1/2) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Brooklyn: York Street M. E. Church (92) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Brooklyn: Zion African Meth Church (93) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Caldwell, John (1) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Calverton, Long Island (1A) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Camp, Harvey (1B) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Campbell, James (2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Campbell, E. A. (2-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Camp Meetings (3) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Canarsie Methodist Protestant Church (3A) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Candee, Homer (4) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Candee, Isaac (5) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Canfield, Ezekiel (6) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Carley, Jesse (7) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Carpenter, Charles W. (8) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Carpenter, Coles (9) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Carpenter, Jr., Lattin (10) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Carr, William (10A) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Carroll, James M. (10B) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cedar Swamp Circuit (10C) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cedar Swamp African M. E. Church (10C) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Centerport M. E. Church (11) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Centerport Meth Prot Church (11-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Central Islip (13) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chadwick, James S. (14) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chapman, Adelbert P. (15) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chapman, John A. (16) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chapman, Melville B. (17) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chase, Henry (18) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cheney, Laban C. (19) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Cheney, Nathan G. (19-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chew, Thomas S. (20) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chichester, Elijah (21) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Christian Hook (22) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Christopher, Robert P. (23) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Churchill, Jay A. (23-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Circular (24) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Clarenceville (24-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Clark, John (26) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Clark, Laban (27) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Clark, L. (28) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Clark, Sylvester H. (29) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Clark, Theodore F. (29-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Clark, Theodosius (30) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Clark, William W. (31) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Clintonville (32) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Cloud, Robert (33) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Celburn, George L. (33) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Cochran, Samuel (34) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    General
    Includes the "Plan of Appointments" for the nine preachers of the New York East Circuit (1834-1835).
  - Codling, Robert (35) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cold Spring Harbor African M. E. Church (36) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cold Spring Harbor M. E. Church (37) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Coleman, James (38) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Coles, George (39) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Collins, William Force (40) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Collord, George W. (41) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Collord, James (41-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Colver, Nathan F. (42) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Commack M. E. Church (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Compton, G. N. (44A) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Compton, M. F. (44B) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Cooke, Horace (45) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Cookman, John E. (45-1/2) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Cooper, Ezekiel (46) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cooper, Rufus T. (46A) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Copeland, H. (46B) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Coram and Fire Place Circuit (47) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Coram, Fire Place and Middle Island Circuit (48) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Coram M. E. Church (49) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Corbit, William P. (50) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Conner, Charles P. (51) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Coach, David W. (51B) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Councils of Ministers (51C) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Court House Class M. E. Church (52) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Covel, James Jr. (53) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cowles, Oliver J. (53A) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cow Neck, see Port Washington (54) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cowper, Charles Philip (55) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cox, Philip (56) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Crawford, John (57) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Corona M. E. Church (57A) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Crawford, Joseph (58) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Crawford, R. S. (58A) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Creagh, Bartholomew (59) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cromlish, John (60) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Crooks, George R. (61) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Crofut, J. H. (61A) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Cunningham, Edward A. (61B) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Curry, Daniel (62) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Curtiss, Edward (62A) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Cutchogue Circuit (63) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cutchogue M. E. Church (64) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cypress Hills, see Brooklyn Andrews M. E. Church (65) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Dalziel, William (1) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Derhain, Clayton (1) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Davenport, Zechariah (1A) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Davies, John (1B) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Samuel C. (2) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Davis, Wesley R. (3) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Dean, Wilfred (4) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dear Park Primitive Methodist Church (5) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - De Hass, Frank S. (6) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Deininger, J. C. (6-1/2) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - De La Matyr, Gilbert (7) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Dempster, James (7A) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Denniston, Eli (8) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - D'Orsay, John S. (9) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - De Vinne, Daniel (10) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dewey, Timothy (11) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Dickens, John (12) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Dickenson, Charles W. (13) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Dickinson, John (13A) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Dickson, W. A. (13B) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Dikeman, George W. (14) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Dikeman, Joseph B. (15) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Dinger, Frederick W. (17) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Diossy, Richard K. (18) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Dix Hills (image included) (19) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dixon, Allen (20) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Dixon, Brachen (21) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Dixon, William (22) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Doering, Charles H. (23) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Donnovan (24) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Douglass, William L. (24-1/4) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Dow, Lorenzo (24-1/2) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Downing, B. F. (24-2/3) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Drake, Samuel (25) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Drummond, Thomas (26) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Duinkerke, J. F. (26-1/2) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Dunbar, George (27) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Dunbar, John (27A) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Dusinburre, G. R. (27B) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Dutcher, Edward H. (28) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Dutch Kills, see L. I. City 3rd Church (29) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Eagan, Abram R. (29A) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Eames, Henry (30) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - East Hampton African M. E. Zion Church (30-1/2) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - East Hampton M. E. Church (31) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - East Manor (31-1/2) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - East Marion (32) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - East Meadow Circuit (33) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - East Meadow M. E. Church (34) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - East Middle Island, see Coram (35) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - East Moriches M. E. Church (36) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - East New York, see Brooklyn, Williams Ave. (37) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - East New York, Wesley Ch. see Brooklyn, Wesley Church (37-1/2) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - East New York, Williams Ave, see Brooklyn, Williams Ave (37-2/3) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Fargher, Joseph (2) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Farmingdale Circuit (3) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Farmingdale Free Methodist Church (4) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Farmingdale M. E. Church (5) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Far Rockaway And Fosters Meadow Circuit (6) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Far Rockaway M. E. Church, see Lawrence (7) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Faucett, Adam C. (8) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fawcett, J. (9) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Ferguson, Samuel D. (10) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ferguson, Sanford I. (image included) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ferris, Daniel O. (11) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Ferris, Ira (12) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Field, Julius (13) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Filmore, George (14) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Finnegan, John (15) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Fire Place, see Brookhaven (16) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fire Place (Brookhaven) Circuit (17) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fisher, G. C. F. (17-1/2) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fitch, William A. (18) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Flanders (19) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Flatbush African M. E. Church (19-1/2) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Flatbush and Flatlands Circuit (20) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Flatbush, Fennimore Street M. E. Church (20A) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Flatbush M. E. Church (image included) (21) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Flatlands M. E. Church (21A) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fletcher, Charles (23) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Floy, James (24) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Flushing African M. E. Church (25) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Flushing Circuit African M. E. Church (26) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Flushing African M. E. Zion Church (26A) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Flushing Circuit M. E. Church (27) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Flushing Ally African M. E. Church (28-1/2) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Flushing M. E. Church (28) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Ford, Calvin B. (29) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Fordham, Charles W. (30) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fordham, Stephen (31) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Fort Hamilton (32) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Foss, Cyrus (33) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Foss, Cyrus David (image included) (34) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Foster, J. M. (34-1/2) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Foster, Randolph S. (35) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Foster, Sylvester (36) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Foster, Thomas (37) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fourth Neck, see Atlanticville (39) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fox, Henry John (image included) (40) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Francis, Abraham S. (41) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Freeport M. E. Church (image included) (42) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Freeport Primitive Meth Church (43) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - French, Mansfield (44) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Freund, John W. (45) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Frost, Joseph H. (46) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Frost, L. P. (47) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Fuller, George L. (48) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Gallagher, Charles W. (1) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Garrettson, Freeborn (2) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Griffin, Charles W. (3) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Gilbert, Gad Smith (4) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Gilbert, Raphael (5) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Gilder, John Leonard (6) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Gilder, William H. (7) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Gill, Joseph H. (7B) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Gillies, William W. (7C) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Gilman, B. A. (7D) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Gladdern, Washington (8) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Glen Cove African M. E. Church (8-1/2) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Glen Cove Circuit African M. E. Church (8-1/3) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Glen Cove Circuit M. E. Church (9) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Glen Cove M. E. Church (10) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Glenwood (11) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Gleuk, Frederick (12) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Glover, Charles E. (13) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Glover, James R. (14) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Goodenough, Arthur H. (15B) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Good Ground (16) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Goodsell, Buel (17) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Goodsell, George H. (18) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Goodsell, Daniel A. (image included) (19) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Gorse, Charles (20) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Gothard, William (21) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Gowanus M.E. Church (21A) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Gracey, J. T. (21B) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Graham, Alexander (22) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Graham, Curtis (23) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Gratz, Francis G. (24) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Graves, Albert S (25) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Graves, George A. (26) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gravesend African M. E. Zion Church (26-1/2) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gravesend M. E. Church, see Unionville (27) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gravesend Meth. Prot. Church (28) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Graw, John J. (29) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Great Neck (30) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Green, John C. (31) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Includes 1850 publication Trial of Rev. John C. Green against John Pierce for slander
  - Green, Lemuel (32) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Greenfield Circuit (33) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Greenfield M. E. Church, see Parkville (34) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Greenpoint First Church, see Brooklyn First Church (34A) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Greenpoint Tabernacle, see Brooklyn Tabernacle (34B) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Greenport African M. E. Zion Church (35) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Greenport and Orient Circuit (36) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Greenport Free Meth Church (37) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Greenport M. E. Church (38) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Griffen, Benjamin (39) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Grimm, Christian F. (40) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Griswold, Edwin E. (41) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Groth, J. C. (42) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Gurney, Samuel (43) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Hadley, Edwin F. (1) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Haff, Isaac W. (2) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Hagany, John B. (3) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Half Hallows (4) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hall, George A. (5) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hall, Jacob (6) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hall, James L. (7) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hallock, Daniel F. (8) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hallock, Frank M. (9) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hamilton, Jay Benson (9A) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hamilton, William (9B) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hammond, Albert O. (10) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hammond, Joseph R. (11) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hammond, Samuel M. (12) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hammond, William (12A) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hanaburgh, D. H. (13) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hand, James Howard (14) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Handgis, Philip (15) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hansen, Martin (15-1/2) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Harden, William (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Harris, Charles Edward (16) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Harris, Reuben (17) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Hatch, J. L. (17-1/2) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hatfield, Henry (18) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hatfield, Robert M. (19) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hatfield, William F. (20) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Haugh, John S. (21) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hauppauge M. E. Church (22) (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Includes 1809 subscription list for building the church at Hauppauge.
  - Hauppauge Burial Ground (22-1/2) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Haynes, Emory J. (image included) (23) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Head of Harbor, see Saint James (24) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Head of River, see Smithtown Landing (25) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Hebard, Elijah (26) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Hebberd, Eben S. (27) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Hedstrom, Oloff G. (28) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Hempstead African M. E. Zion Church (28B) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Hempstead Huntington Circuit (29) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Hempstead Branch Class (30) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Hempstead Circuit M. E. Church (31) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hempstead Harbor Circuit (32) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hempstead Harbor, see Roslyn (33) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hempstead M. E. Church (34) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hempstead South Class, see Freeport (35) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Hempstead South East Class, see Simons Neck (36) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Hempstead West, see Fosters Meadow (37) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Henderson, Theodore S. (image only) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Henson, Joseph (38) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hertel, Charles Augustus (39) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Hibbard, Billy (40) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Hicks, John (41) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hicks, William Henry (42) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hicks Chapel African M. E. Church (42-1/2) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hicks Neck M. E. Church (43) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hickson, Woolman (44) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Hicksville M. E. Church (45) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Hicksville German M. E. Church (46) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Hicksville Meth Prot Church (46-1/2) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Hicksville Meth Prot (47) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Hicks Neck Meth Prot Church (48) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Hill, Arza (48-1/2) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Hill, Francis (49) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Hill, George (50) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hill, William T. (51) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Hollis, George (51) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Holmes, David (52) (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Holmes, Wesley Levi (53) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Horne, James Wesley (54) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Howard, T. P. (54A) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Howard, William (55) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Howe, Bezaleel (56) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Howe, John M. (57) (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Howe, Philimon W. (58) (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Howell, F. G. (59) (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Howland, Seneca (60) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Hoyt, William B. (61) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Hoyt, William C. (62) (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Hubbard, Reuben (63) (Box 7, Folder 49)
    Includes 1860 publication An address delivered in St. John's Church, Yonkers, N.Y., at the funeral services of the Rev. Reuben Hubbard.
  - Hubbell, George A. (64) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Hubbell, Nathan (65) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Hulin, Alexander (66) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Humphreys, Humphrey (67) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Hunt, Aaron (68) (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Hunt, Aaron Jr. (69) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hunt, Albert S. (70) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hunt, Hoyt E. (70-1/2) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hunt, Jesse (71) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hunter's Point, see Long Island City (72-1/8) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Huntington African M. E. Church (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Huntington Circuit African M. E. Church (72-1/2) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Huntington Circuit M. E. Church (73) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Huntington M. E. Church (74) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Huntington South Circuit M. E. Church (75) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Includes attendance record of members for Hempstead and Huntington (1829-1833).
  - Husted, Harvey (76) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hutchinson, Robert (77) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Includes two certificates (with wax seal) from Francis Asbury naming Hutchinson deacon and elder (1791, 1794).
  - Hutchinson, Sylvester (78) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Illman, Robert (1) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Inskip, John S. (2) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Islip African M. E. Zion Church (3) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Islip M. E. Church (Image included) (4) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Islip East, see Islip (5) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Islip Great Neck, see Islip (6) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Islip North, see Islip (7) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Islip South, see Islip (Hubbs) (8) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Islip West, see Islip (9) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Items Miscellaneous (10) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Jagger, Ezra (11) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Jamaica African M. E. Church (12) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Jamaica and Rockaway Circuit, see Rockaway (12-1/2) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Jamaica African M. E. Zion Church (13) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Jamaica Circuit African M. E. Church (14) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Jamaica Circuit M. E. Church (15) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Jamesport (17) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Janes, Edwin Lines (18) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Jayne, George S. (19) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Jayne, Peter (20) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Jefferies, William (20A) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Jeffrey, John (21) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Jericho African M. E. Church (22) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Jericho M. E. Church (23) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Jerusalem African M. E. Zion Church (24) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jerusalem M. E. Church (25) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jerusalem German M. E. Church (26) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jerusalem M. E. Church Colored Class (27) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jerusalem South, see Seaford (28) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jessop, Robert (29) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Jewett, William (30) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Johansen, B. (31) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Johns, John (31A) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Johnson, Matthew (32) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Johnson, Samuel F. (33) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Jones, Daniel (34) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Jones, Edwin F. (35) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Jones, Robert W. (36) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Jost, Caspar (37) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Judd, Horace (37A) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Kastendick, Henry (37B) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Kastendieck, H. F. (37C) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Kavanaugh, A. S. (38) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Keeler, Denton (39) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Keeler, Samuel C. (40) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Kelly, A. B. (41) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Kelly, William V. (42) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Kellogg, Nathaniel (43) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Kelsey, Charles (44) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kendall, David (45) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Kennaday, John (47) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Kitchabonnock (48) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Kettell, George F. (50) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Kindler, Jacob (51) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - King, C. W. (51A) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - King, Samuel Warner (52) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Kirby, Francis G. (53) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Kirby, Richard D. (54) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Kirk, J. H. (55) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Kline, John (56) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Kling, William H. (57) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Kuesal, C. A. (58) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Kristeller, Siegfried (59) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Kunst, Hermann (19) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Kurth, William H. (20) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Long Island Circuit and Suffolk Circuit (7) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lane, Orsin C. (7) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Langlois, John L. (8) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Lansing, Isaac J. (9) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lasby, Charles C. (10) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Latham, Henry D. (11) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lathbury, Albert A. (12) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lathbury, Clarence (12A) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lattinstown (13) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - La Valle, James (14) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Law, Joseph (image included) (15) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Law, Samuel W. (16) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Lawrence M. E. Church, formerly Far Rockaway (16A) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lawrence Meth. Prot. Church (17) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence, William (18) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence, W. H. (19) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Layton, W. A. (20) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Leach, A. J. (21) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Lee, John (22) (Box 9, Folder 10)